hkmarathon.com 2013-12-02

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

**Privacy Policy**

  1. Hong Kong Amateur Athletic Association (HKAAA) collects personal information when you register as a runner of Standard Chartered Hong Kong Marathon 2014. When you register we ask for your personal information such as your name, HKID / Passport, nationality, email address, birth date, gender, phone numbers, fax number, address and etc. Such personal information will be collected, stored and used for authentication purpose during registration, or when you utilize our service.
  2. HKAAA will also collect, store and use such personal information for the following general purposes: to customize the sport of athletics (including the marathon) or runners information, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research. HKAAA may further use such personal information and/or provide such personal information to another person (including agent, contractor or third party service provider who provides administrative, telecommunications and computer service to HKAAA in connection with the operation of its business) for direct marketing purpose in relation to sports events and general promotions of the sport of athletics (including the Marathon), or HKAAA agents, sponsors, authorized related parties, companies and organizations connected with any other HKAAA events promotions, but HKAAA may not do so unless your written consent to such use and provision is received.

**Use of Cookies**

Your visiting of our Website (that is [www.hkmarathon.com](http://www.hkmarathon.com/), but apart from those hyperlinked services which are subject to arrangements in their original Websites) may trigger our use of cookies. Cookies used (if any) in any part of our Websites will not be deployed for collecting personally identifiable information. If cookies are deployed for collecting personally identifiable information in the future, we will make separate notices accordingly.

For your information, Cookies are small computer files that can be stored in web surfers' computers for the purposes of obtaining configuration information and analyzing web surfers' viewing habits. They can save you from registering again when re-visiting a Website and are commonly used to track your preferences in relation to the subject matter of the Website. You may refuse to accept Cookies (by modifying the relevant Internet options or browsing preferences of your computer system), but you may not be able to utilize or activate certain available functions in our Websites as the result.

**Security Practices**

HKAAA uses secure servers to protect all of your personal information including your name, address and credit card information. Please remember that no data transmission over the Internet, or by other means, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Disclaimer**

HKAAA expressly disclaims any responsibility for any loss arising out of the online entry in Standard Chartered Hong Kong Marathon 2014.

**Linking Policy**

This site contains links to other sites and pages which are not maintained or controlled by the HKAAA and for which the HKAAA is not responsible. When you activate any of these links or pages you leave the HKAAA's and access to such a site or page is at your own risk for which HKAAA disclaims all responsibility and liability.
